{
    "id": "7f9ce43661034b299f924470e13a0c36",
    "title": "To, with and by: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5045e09eaaf9480e9c1f9167bea3d470",
            "title": "To, With And By",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Be patient …………………… .. children.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "with",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I parted ………………… her after many years of courtship.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "from",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Oil does not mix ..................................... water.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "with",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Are you ....................................... me or against me in this matter?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "for",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let me know ........................................ tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "within",
                        "by"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Somebody has just gone ...................................... the window.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "by",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is two o’clock ......................................... my watch.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "by",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our team won the match ..................................... six goals to three.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "with",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We stayed .......................................... the end of the play.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I prefer walking ........................................ climbing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}